



# ALEJANDRO MARTÍN

3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR

- alehamartinva@gmail.com
- +34 671 213 938
- https://alehaaaa.github.io/
- Berlin, Germany Barcelona, Spain

PROFILE

I am a 3D character animator with intuition and an eye for detail. Experienced in production environments, receiving feedback from the Animation Director and Supervisor and collaborating with other Animators and the Rigging team, always pursuing a more efficient pipeline with custom scripts and tools.

I am excited to join a team-working production and start animating!

## EDUCATION

#### MASTER IN 3D CHARACTER ANIMATION

ECIB | 2021 - 2022

Lip-sync · Advanced Acting

#### **DEGREE IN ANIMATION**

ECIB | 2019 - 2021

 $2D \cdot StopMotion \cdot 3D$ 

ACTING INTRODUCTION EÒLIA THEATER SCHOOL 2021 - 2022

#### TOOLS

M AUTODESK MAYA

**U** ANIMBOT

🏖 PYTHON

SHOTGRID

#### LANGUAGES

English (C1, Advanced)
Spanish (Native)
Catalan (Native)

## EXPERIENCE

# JUNIOR/MID 3D ANIMATOR - DIE SCHULE DER MAGISCHEN TIERE 4 LUMATIC (BERLIN, GERMANY) | NOV 2024 - CURRENTLY

Researched and explored a more stylized animation look through a new character. Continued to collaborate with the Supervisor and Director.

# JUNIOR 3D ANIMATOR - DIE SCHULE DER MAGISCHEN TIERE 3 LUMATIC (BERLIN, GERMANY) | NOV 2023 - JUN 2024

Brought ideas in and, through collaborative teamwork, enhanced the animation with pipeline improvements and the development of tools.

- Animated a variety of animal characters with lip-syncs, studying references and learning about their anatomical behaviours.
- Received feedback directly from the Animation Director.
- Team-worked to push sequences to their best acting potential.
- Improved the animation pipeline creating custom tools and scripts.

# 3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR FOR SHORT FILM - EL MEGA ROBO ECIB (CINEMA SCHOOL OF BARCELONA) | OCT 2022 - SEP 2023

Collaboration with the Director and animators, creating the story from the ground up all together.  $\,$ 

- Developed character traits, maintaining personalities throughout the story, with the tight guidance of the Supervisor.
- Worked on a pose Library and test animations.